<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Portfolio</title><link>https://0x5bjorn.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on Portfolio</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-gb</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://0x5bjorn.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>0x13hrafnulf's Challenges</title><link>https://0x5bjorn.github.io/blog/dll-inj/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://0x5bjorn.github.io/blog/dll-inj/</guid><description>Who is 0x13hrafnulf?
Simple DLL injector with GUI (dll-inj) in development
Simple DLL injector with GUI written in C++ for educational purposes only
Demo Code organization source code
GUI - GUI management using Dear ImGui Injection - DLL injection implemention using Windows API OpenDialogBox - file selection dialog box using Windows API Proc - process and process modules querying handler Application - application and app window management Description Coming soon&amp;hellip;</description></item><item><title>System Info visualizer</title><link>https://0x5bjorn.github.io/portfolio/si-vis-project/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://0x5bjorn.github.io/portfolio/si-vis-project/</guid><description>System Info visualizer (si-vis) in development
Simple system info visualizer written in Rust for educational purposes only
Dependency resolution eframe - official framework library for writing apps using egui, GUI library for Rust egui_dock - library provides docking(tabs) support for egui egui_extras - adds some features on top of egui, used for building table sysinfo - crate used to get a system&amp;rsquo;s information Code organization si_gui, contains GUI app drawing and updating parts si_data, stores and updates system info data Screenshots General system info tab CPU and its usage info tab Processes info table tab Future plans Change UI from egui to ratatui Reorganize app layout Add sorting based on columns in processes info table Display memory allocations in real-time when specific process is selected (inspired by mevi)</description></item><item><title>User Mode thread Scheduling</title><link>https://0x5bjorn.github.io/portfolio/aosv-ums-project/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://0x5bjorn.github.io/portfolio/aosv-ums-project/</guid><description>AOSV Final Project Report A.Y. 2020/2021
Introduction The goal of the project was to implement User Mode thread Scheduling mechanism for the Linux distribution, inspired by the User-mode scheduling (UMS) implementation available in the Windows kernel [1]. UMS is a mechanism that allows applications/programs in the user mode to schedule their own threads without involving the kernel/system scheduler. The main goal and advantage is that thread switching in user mode is &amp;ldquo;more efficient than thread pools for managing large numbers of short-duration work items that require few system calls.</description></item><item><title>Hugo Portfolio Website</title><link>https://0x5bjorn.github.io/projects/hugo-portfolio-website/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2020 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://0x5bjorn.github.io/projects/hugo-portfolio-website/</guid><description>I created my portfolio website using Hugo and UIKit, it serves as an online resume containing all my work.
This has been created as a theme so that others can use and adapt it.
Sections Homepage The homepage provides the basic information about you, including links to social media, skills you have, things you&amp;rsquo;ve done and your education. This page makes good use of UIKit grid and cards for organising all the information and ensuring it is responsive to work on mobile devices.</description></item><item><title>Team project without GitHub</title><link>https://0x5bjorn.github.io/projects/example-team-no-github/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2020 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://0x5bjorn.github.io/projects/example-team-no-github/</guid><description>This is some content</description></item></channel></rss>