<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Portfolio</title><link>https://umarbaev-s.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on Portfolio</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-gb</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://umarbaev-s.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>User Mode thread Scheduling</title><link>https://umarbaev-s.github.io/portfolio/aosv-ums-project/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://umarbaev-s.github.io/portfolio/aosv-ums-project/</guid><description>AOSV Final Project Report A.Y. 2020/2021
Introduction The goal of the project was to implement User Mode thread Scheduling mechanism for the Linux distribution, inspired by the User-mode scheduling (UMS) implementation available in the Windows kernel [1]. UMS is a mechanism that allows applications/programs in the user mode to schedule their own threads without involving the kernel/system scheduler. The main goal and advantage is that thread switching in user mode is &amp;ldquo;more efficient than thread pools for managing large numbers of short-duration work items that require few system calls.</description></item><item><title>Hugo Portfolio Website</title><link>https://umarbaev-s.github.io/projects/hugo-portfolio-website/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2020 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://umarbaev-s.github.io/projects/hugo-portfolio-website/</guid><description>I created my portfolio website using Hugo and UIKit, it serves as an online resume containing all my work.
This has been created as a theme so that others can use and adapt it.
Sections Homepage The homepage provides the basic information about you, including links to social media, skills you have, things you&amp;rsquo;ve done and your education. This page makes good use of UIKit grid and cards for organising all the information and ensuring it is responsive to work on mobile devices.</description></item><item><title>Team project without GitHub</title><link>https://umarbaev-s.github.io/projects/example-team-no-github/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2020 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://umarbaev-s.github.io/projects/example-team-no-github/</guid><description>This is some content</description></item><item><title>Making a new Website</title><link>https://umarbaev-s.github.io/blog/first-blog/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2019 12:14:34 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://umarbaev-s.github.io/blog/first-blog/</guid><description>For a long time this website has had a couple of links to contact me, but those days are over.
Now I have a brand new Hugo website with a custom written theme complete with
A homepage with more social links, and description of my skills An about page with description of who I am A portfolio page to showcase all my projects A blog Why Hugo? The first question is why a site builder?</description></item></channel></rss>